Finding Aid for Republican Party (Mich.). State Central Committee Records ca. 1958-1979
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Photographs
  - Individuals [primarily portraits; complete listing of names available in collection]
    - A-Z, 38 folders
      - Burdick, Irwin (Box 71)
      - Bursley, Gilbert E. (Box 71)
      - Busfield, Roger (Box 71)
      - Buth, Martin D. (Box 71)
      - Byker, Gzary (Box 71)
      - Byrnes, James W. (Box 71)
      - Calcutt, Harry (Box 71)
      - Calhoun, David G. (Box 71)
      - Calvin, Ben (Box 71)
      - Cargo, David F. (Box 71)
      - Carlson, Frank (Box 71)
      - Carr, James E. (Box 71)
      - Carr, Leland W., Jr. (Box 71)
      - Carroll, Howard R. (Box 71)
      - Caswell, Dorothy C. (Box 71)
      - Cawthorne, Dennis (Box 71)
      - Cederberg, Elford A. (Box 71)
      - Chamberlain, Charles E. (Box 71)
      - Chandler, Paul (Box 71)
      - Charlton, Fred. (Box 71)
      - Clark, Lee (Box 71)
      - Clements, John Vaughan (Box 71)
      - Clements, Mrs. John Vaughan (Box 71)
      - Cobb, Andrew (Box 71)
      - Conlin, Rollo G. (Box 71)
      - Connelly, Brien (Box 71)
      - Corden, James (Box 71)
      - Corning, Glen (Box 71)
      - Cudlip, William B. [with George Romney] (Box 71)
      - Czarnecki, Walter (Box 71)
      - Danhof, Robert J. (Box 71)
      - Degrow, Alvin (Box 71)
      - Dehmel, Arthur (Box 71)
      - DeMaso, Harry A. (Box 71)
      - Dempsey, John T. (Box 71)
      - Dethmers, John R. (Box 71)
      - DeVries, Walter D. (Box 71)
      - Diehl, Dave (Box 71)
      - Ditmer, Robert [campaign billboard only] (Box 71)
      - Dively, Michael (Box 71)
      - Dow, Douglas (Box 71)
      - Downs, Nancy (Box 71)
      - Doyle, John [with William Milliken] (Box 71)
      - Dyell, Mary (Box 71)
      - Eastlick, Mike [with William Milliken] (Box 71)
      - Elder, Stanley W. (Box 71)
      - Elliott, Arthur G. [with George Romney at 1964 Republican National Convention] (Box 71)
      - Elston, Dorothy (Box 71)
      - Ernst, Richard D. (Box 71)
      - Esch, Marvin [with Gerald Ford] (Box 71)
      - Farhat, Leo A. (Box 71)
      - Feikens, John (Box 71)
      - Finegan, George W. (Box 71)
      - Fitzgerald, John W. (Box 71)
      - Fleming, James G. (Box 71)
      - Fowler, Albert C. (Box 71)
      - Francis, Lynn O. (Box 71)
      - Gallagher, Kenneth (Box 71)
      - Geake, R. Robert (Box 71)
      - Gibbs, John A. (Box 71)
      - Geerings, Clyde (Box 71)
      - Gillis, John (Box 71)
      - Goldwater, Barry (Box 71)
      - Grant, Lisa [with William Milliken] (Box 71)
      - Grant, Robert W. (Box 71)
      - Greene, Jean Seeley (Box 71)
      - Greenwald, Mrs. Arthur E. (Box 71)
      - Griffin, Robert [include 1972 campaign and one photo with Spiro Agnew, Gerald Ford, and others] (Box 71)
      - Grimes, Thomas P. (Box 71)
      - Groat, Gustave J. (Box 71)
      - Groesbeck, Harvey J. (Box 71)
      - Gusman, Max [with William Milliken] (Box 71)
      - Harvey, James (Box 71)
      - Hatch, Raymond N [with George Romney] (Box 71)
      - Hayner, Isabel (Box 71)
      - Heinlen, Dave (Box 71)
      - Heinze, James H. (Box 71)
      - Higgins, George N. (Box 71)
      - Hippler, Leonard (Box 71)
      - Hobbs, Ruth (Box 71)
      - Hobbs, Wendell W. (Box 71)
      - Holbrook, Donald E. (Box 71)
      - Huber, Robert J. (Box 71)
      - Huebner, Trudy (Box 71)
      - Hughes, Harold B. (Box 71)
      - Hungerford, Harold W. (Box 71)
      - Hutchinson, Edward (Box 71)
      - Illinik, B. (Box 71)
      - Jeannette, Frank [with William Milliken] (Box 71)
      - Johansen, August E. (Box 71)
      - Johnson, Ernest (Box 71)
      - Jones, Betty (Box 71)
      - Jones, Cathy [with William Milliken] (Box 71)
      - Karam, Arthur [with William Milliken] (Box 71)
      - Kasten, August (Box 71)
      - Keesler, John (Box 71)
      - Kelly, Harry F. (Box 71)
      - Kelly, Sid S. [with George Romney] (Box 71)
      - Kennedy, Charles S. (Box 71)
      - Kennedy, Earl (Box 71)
      - Kennedy, William (Box 71)
      - Klei, Louis W. (Box 71)
      - Knapp, William (Box 71)
      - Knill, H. Charles (Box 71)
      - Koernke, Thomas F. (Box 71)
      - Koeze, Ellen (Box 71)
      - Kok, Peter (Box 71)
      - Kolderman, Johannes C., Jr. (Box 71)
      - Koppy, Walter [with George Romney during 1968 campaign] (Box 71)
      - Kuhn, George W. (Box 71)
      - Kuhn, Richard (Box 71)
      - Laporte, Alfred (Box 71)
      - Little, Carl O. (Box 71)
      - Lodge, L. Harvey (Box 71)
      - Logan, Mrs. Kenneth (Box 71)
      - McCormick, Edward J. (Box 71)
      - McDonald, Jack (Box 71)
      - McGoff, John P. (Box 71)
      - McGregor, Louis D [1962 campaign] (Box 71)
      - McIntosh, Robert J. (Box 71)
      - MacKenzie, Clark W. (Box 71)
      - McLaughlin, William F. (Box 71)
      - McMillan, Mary Louise [with Helen Milliken] (Box 71)
      - Mantey, Carl F. (Box 71)
      - Mapes, Laura (Box 71)
      - Martin, John B. (Box 71)
      - Maxon, Thomas (Box 71)
      - May, Alfred A. (Box 71)
      - Meany, Edward, Jr. (Box 71)
      - Megill, Dixie (Box 71)
      - Meissner, Charles (Box 71)
      - Menhennick, Alva (Box 71)
      - Merriman, Frank (Box 71)
      - Miles, Wendell A. (Box 71)
      - Miller, Allan C. (Box 71)
      - Miller, Jack (Box 71)
      - Miller, William (Box 71)
      - Milliken, William G. (Box 71)
      - Moeller, William (Box 71)
      - Moore, Franklin (Box 71)
      - Morrison, Clayton T. (Box 71)
      - Nair, Lois V. (Box 71)
      - Nash, Ernest W. (Box 71)
      - Nisbet, Stephen S. (Box 71)
      - Nixon, Richard M. [with George Romney, Ronald Reagan, and others] (Box 71)
      - Numelly (?), James S. (Box 71)
      - O'Hara, Michael D. (Box 71)
      - O'Neil, James F. [with George Romney] (Box 71)
      - O'Neill, Richard (Box 71)
      - Pahl, Marion (Box 71)
      - Parson, Robert D. (Box 71)
      - Payant, John D. (Box 71)
      - Pears, Don R. (Box 71)
      - Perras, Clifford (Box 71)
      - Perria, Eugene E. (Box 71)
      - Peterson, Elly [with George Romney, Edward Brooks and others] (Box 71)
      - Pfeiffer, Lillian (Box 71)
      - Phelan, Ellen (Box 71)
      - Piggins, Edward (Box 71)
      - Plank, Raymond A. (Box 71)
      - Plans, Don (Box 71)
      - Powell, Stanley M. (Box 71)
      - Prescott, George A. (Box 71)
      - Puls, Edwin E. (Box 71)
      - Pushan, David R. (Box 71)
      - Ray, Sherman (Box 71)
      - Raviolo, Victor G. (Box 71)
      - Reid, Clarence A. (Box 71)
      - Rice, Mary G. (Mrs. Stewart M.) (Box 71)
      - Richardson, Robert L. (Box 71)
      - Riecker, Margaret [with Robert Griffin and Lenore Romney] (Box 71)
      - Riethmiller, Gorton (Box 71)
      - Roberts, Farrell E. (Box 71)
      - Robinson, D. (Box 71)
      - Robinson, Milt [with William Milliken] (Box 71)
      - Romney, George [one with William Milliken] (Box 71)
      - Romney, Lenore (Box 71)
      - Rourke, Peter (Box 71)
      - Rowley, H. (Box 71)
      - Rush, Carl (Box 71)
      - Russler, Wayne (Box 71)
      - Sanderson, Louis (Box 71)
      - Seidman, L. William [with George Romney] (Box 71)
      - Shuttleworth, Billy (Box 71)
      - Smart, Clifford (Box 71)
      - Smith, Henry B. (Box 71)
      - Smith, James F. (Box 71)
      - Smith, Nick (Box 71)
      - Smith, Richard G. [with George Romney] (Box 71)
      - Spencer, Roy L. (Box 71)
      - Stein, Ivan (Box 71)
      - Stevens, Earl L. (Box 71)
      - Stephens, J. Harold J. (Box 71)
      - Stockmeyer, Norman O. [one with William Milliken, one photo of 1962 campaign] (Box 71)
      - Taber (Box 71)
      - Taylor, Clair L. (Box 71)
      - Thompson, Kenneth W. (Box 71)
      - Thorburn, Albert J. (Box 71)
      - Tisdale, Nelson G. (Box 71)
      - Toepp, John F. (Box 71)
      - Tomasik, Ron (Box 71)
      - Tomlins, C. S. (Box 71)
      - Tool, Jean K. (Box 71)
      - Tower, John [with Elly Peterson] (Box 71)
      - Towns, Fred B. (Box 71)
      - Truax, Craig (Box 71)
      - Tyson, Charles E. (?) (Box 71)
      - Upton, David (Box 71)
      - Vander Loan, Robert (Box 71)
      - Van Dusen, Richard C. (Box 71)
      - Van Lare, Stanley (Box 71)
      - Van Peursem, George M. (Box 71)
      - VanderJagt, Guy (Box 71)
      - Vanderziel, Leo (Box 71)
      - Van Rensselaer, Bernard S. (Box 71)
      - Varnum, Charles (Box 71)
      - Ver Duin, Claude (Box 71)
      - Vernon, John (Box 71)
      - Vincent, Dwight H. (Box 71)
      - Volkema, Harold J. (Box 71)
      - Waldron, Robert (Box 71)
      - Walker, Richard W. (Box 71)
      - Warner, Dale (Box 71)
      - Warshawsky, Meyer (Box 71)
      - Washington, George (Box 71)
      - Weber, William V. (Box 71)
      - Welborn, Jack (Box 71)
      - White, Ink [with George Romney] (Box 71)
      - Whittaker, Alfred H. (Box 71)
      - Whittaker, Hilary [with Elly Peterson and George Romney] (Box 71)
      - Williams, Clara B. (Box 71)
      - Wismer, Don (Box 71)
      - Wright, Della M. (Box 71)
      - Wright, Lillian (Mrs. Bruce Wright) (Box 71)
      - Yeager, Weldon O. (Box 71)
      - Yeager, Wirt (Box 71)
      - Yemen, Arpo (Box 71)
      - Zaagman, Milton (Box 71)
      - Zeeb, Robert (Box 71)
      - Zollar, Charles O. (Box 71)
    - Candidates 1966 (Box 71)
    - Republican State Central Committee members (Box 71)
    - Republican Women's Federation (Box 71)
    - Republican National Convention delegates 1976 (Box 71)
    - Urban campaign slides (Box 71)
    - Voter fraud, 1962 (Box 71)
      (includes photos of polling places in Detroit, solicitation of voters, and vacant lots)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 71)
      (includes some 1962 campaign photos)